https://www.zicam.com/privacy-policy/

Zicam® | Privacy Policy For Your Use Of The www.zicam.com Website
Save $2.00
on ONE
Zicam Product and $5.00 on TWO Zicam Products >>
Our Products Where to Buy WHY ZICAM® FAQs Our Products Where to Buy WHY ZICAM® FAQsZicam Cold Remedy About Zicam Products About the Common Cold Cold Viruses Common Cold Facts and Myths Cold Prevention Zinc and Colds About Homeopathy Cold or Allergies Cold or FluCold ShorteningLozengesMedicated Fruit DropsNasal SprayNasal SwabsOral Mist™Original RapidMelts®ULTRA RapidMelts®Cold Shortening + ElderberryCitrus Elderberry RapidMelts®Elderberry Medicated Fruit DropsNasal Congestion/Sinus ReliefNasal AllClear™Extreme Congestion ReliefIntense Sinus ReliefAllergy ReliefAllergy Relief SwabsAllergy ReliefZicam Cold RemedyAbout Zicam ProductsAbout the Common ColdCold VirusesCommon Cold Facts and MythsCold PreventionZinc and ColdsAbout HomeopathyCold or AllergiesCold or Flu
PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy applies to the www.zicam.com website, as well as to online promotions, sweepstakes and contests sponsored by Matrixx Initiatives, Inc. (collectively, the "Site"). This Privacy Policy describes the information that Matrixx Initiatives, Inc. ("we" or "us") collects on the Site, how we may use it, and with whom we may share it. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this Site or providing personally identifiable information to us for any promotion, sweepstakes or contest. The Site is intended for use by residents of the United States.Your Consent By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.About Children This Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this Site from visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information that they disclose to Web sites.Information You Provide Some areas of this Site may ask you to submit personally identifiable information in order for you to benefit from specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions) or to participate in a particular activity (such as contacting us with questions or comments). The personally identifiable information that we may collect includes contact information, such as your name, email address, or zip code; information about your intended or actual use of our products; and certain other information you may provide to us in your communications, including information about your health or physical condition. You do not have to provide your personally identifiable information to use the Site, but if you do not, that may limit the features that you are able to access through the Site. We generally will take steps to inform you of what information is required and what information is optional for a given feature.Passive Information Collection As you navigate through this Site, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without you actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). Your Internet browser automatically transmits to this Site some of this information, such as the URL of the Web site that referred you to the Site, the Internet Protocol (IP) address, and the browser version that your computer or device currently is using. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this Site might not work without cookies. This Site does not honor or respond to a web browser's "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that provide users with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party sites or online services. This Site does not allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different Web sites when you use this Site.Third parties, including Amazon, may place and use pixels on this Site to show interest-based ads to you.
If you do not want to receive interest-based ads from Amazon, you can opt out by visiting the relevant Amazon Advertising Preferences page, the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, or YourOnlineChoices page for your location.Use and Disclosure of Information We may use information collected via this Site to do various things, including: to administer or improve the Site; to customize the Site to your preferences; to communicate information to you if you have requested it through features such as the "Contact Us" page; to send you newsletters, exclusive offers, and promotions; to provide you with the products, services, and information that you request; to perform business analyses or for other activities to improve the quality of our Site, or other products and services that we offer; to compile and analyze statistics and trends; for marketing and research purposes; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.If you provide personally identifiable information to this Site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We also may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this Site to other entities, including authorized service providers or contractors that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as to host the Site, manage databases, or provide certain components of the Site); in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a sale, assignment, merger, divestiture, bankruptcy, reorganization, liquidation, or other transfer of the business or its assets; to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations; to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal activities, fraud, or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, you, or any third party; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent. We do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.Access, Correction and Deletion To keep personally identifiable information that you provide via this Site accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below and we will take appropriate steps to update or correct such information in our possession, or to delete your information from our contact list.Security This Site takes reasonable steps to help protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our Site and to help protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. As a result, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of information that you transmit via the Site and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of personally identifiable information.Links to other Web Sites This Site may contain links or references to other Web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every Web site you visit.How to Contact Us If you have any questions, comments, requests, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Site, or if you would like to opt out of future communications, please contact us as follows:Zicam® Customer Service 1-877-942-2626, toll free ZicamCS@safetycall.comChanges to This Privacy Policy If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this Site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. The effective date of this policy is: July 15, 2019. satisfaction guaranteed.Our ProductsWhere to BuyWHY ZICAM®FAQsCONTACT USTERMS OF USEPRIVACY POLICYSITE MAP©2020, Matrixx Initiatives, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Follow us
